Last time on Zombieland Saga, we ironed out some of the details about our name and group leader.
We decided Saki should be in charge, and that our group's called Franchuchu.
That really screams cute zombie girls, don't you think?
Once that was all squared away, we had a gorilla-style pop-up show in the street.
It was our first time doing anything idyllish, and that was cool, but it's pretty clear we have a long way to go.
We'll have to keep practicing till we die all over again.
But I believe in me, and I believe in Franchuchu!
Good morning, ladies!
Oh, come on, you look like you're dead inside!
Good morning!
Good morning to you too, sir.
Okay, first thing, it looks like you've been taking your lessons pretty seriously lately.
By the way, how have you been settling into your new name?
Franchuchu?
You're saying it wrong, it's Franchuchu!
Franny Fanny Chuchu!
Franchuchu!
Yeah, yeah, I know, it's Flannel Fufu!
We have a French name, look how cute we are!
Okay, Franchuchuchu, even though only a month ago at that gorilla concert, you were still just a brain-dead gaggle of drooling zombies,
you all may have improved the tiniest bit.
And this is the part where the real game begins.
Right, boss?
Uh, yeah, I guess.
Spoken like a true leader.
What's your take on it, Lily?
Me? I'll do it!
Great!
Ah!
Now, which one of you ladies would like to guess what your next move should be?
Sakura!
Oh!
I'm not sure.
Maybe it's time for us to record a single and put it out?
Excellent!
You've got a good head on your shoulders!
Let me just call up a recording studio and-
No, dumbass!
Are you crazy?
Where are we gonna get the money?
You honestly think I made a single buck off of you and your raggedy-ass performances so far?
Not to mention your expenses!
Somebody's gotta make sure there's gas in the van, you dumb zombie!
My point is, our budget's as dry as your skin.
Huh?
So what's your plan?
The only solution is get more money.
I'm sorry, what?
Does Saga even have businesses that would hire idols?
Thanks to my supreme awesomeness, yes!
And it's a big-name pharmaceutical company known as Hisanaka!
We can form a partnership if this goes well!
Partnership?
This is way over my head.
Just tell me when it's supposed to go down.
We start right now.
Now?
The old group they had booked for their company trip is no longer available.
Your ideas are so last minute.
Cause we can't afford to miss any chances!
Idols have a limited shelf life nowadays, you know?
And it's not like I can work you girls to death, am I right?
We're doing it and that's final.
Just don't stop practicing!
We have to knock their socks off!
Next up, the Urishino Hot Springs.
Hot Springs?
So we get to take a real bath?
We've just been hosing off in the yard!
Perhaps this is the perfect opportunity to cleanse a bit of stench and decay from our rancid flesh.
They're kind enough to let us stay the night, so please behave yourselves.
We get to stay?
That means plenty of time to chill out!
There will be no hot springs fun for you!
Cause you won't be able to leave your rooms unless you're in your full makeup!
Sucks to be you!
And besides, if you've got time to splish splash in a hot spring, then you've got time to practice!
Ow!
Sir?
What's that?
This pharmaceutical company.
Do they sell pills, or...?
Check it out!
Sagan...ship...sea?
This pharmaceutical company.
Do they sell pills, or...?
Check it out!
Sagan...ship...sea?
See?
Okay, you're room number 606. You go on at 6 p.m., got it?
Understood, sir.
I went to the trouble of reserving a rehearsal space for you, so you girls better practice while I'm gone.
Of course. Wait, what will you be doing, Mr. Kotaro?
Sightseeing.
The sightseekers see themselves!
Okie dokie, where do we want to go first?
Uh, to the room?
Of all the cool stuff we could do, you really pick work.
We should practice.
Yeah, later. Not while Shades is out painting the town without a care in the world.
No, now.
Look, do you want to die?
Come on, we've been cooped up in the house for a solid month.
Let's take advantage of Urashino while we're here.
I want to go for a walk.
The squirt knows what's up.
I said my name's Lily, not Squirt.
I suppose we can relax for a bit.
I haven't seen a modern-day city yet, and I'd like to explore.
We look totally normal with makeup.
If we're super careful, no one will be able to tell we're zombies.
Good thinking, Squirt.
My name is Lily.
If that's what we all want.
Aye, Junko, what's your vote?
It seems risky, but...
Listen to this, Junko.
That sculpture is said to make you healthier and help your skin.
You have to splash water on it.
Let's do it.
Damn, look at him go.
Crazy.
Uh-huh.
It's such an honor to hear from an esteemed company like Hisanaka Pharmaceuticals.
We heard about you from the people who manage the inn.
How fortuitous that my regular interactions with local businesses in the Chamber of Commerce has led us to this encounter.
A Saga-based idol group? That must be hard these days.
It can feel like we're fighting the flow of history.
But the way I see it, if we make even the smallest impact, it's all worth it.
That's wonderful.
We're planning to bring new life to Saga.
As a matter of fact, that idea is at the core of every endeavor Franshushu undertakes.
New life to Saga.
Right.
You and I may be in two different fields, but my group has a great admiration for your company's standing as one of the biggest in the prefecture.
Well, I appreciate the kind words, but we're actually working on ways to expand our overall customer base.
We would like for our brand to appeal to a younger demographic.
In that case, we might just be what you're looking for.
If we were to become partners, I'm confident we could meet and exceed your expectations.
I'm looking forward to this evening's performance, then.
That's excellent to hear.
My hardworking girls are practicing their hearts, so...
Right...
Now.
Is something the matter?
Oh.
Oh, wow.
This feels great.
I've never used one before.
Nothing short of heavenly.
It's still a little crazy that this is happening, though.
What do you mean?
Well, if we hadn't come back from the dead, the seven of us would never have gotten the chance to meet each other.
Because we're all from different times, you know?
Oh, yeah.
And the best part is I don't feel dead.
It's not too bad.
Even if we were alive at the same time, I wouldn't have hung out with Saga.
Shut your yap!
Well, honestly, you all make me feel like I'm a young girl again.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
It must be so different for you.
But bodies are cremated in Japan.
So how'd we get like this?
I'm a little curious about Mr. Tatsumi.
Don't look at me!
Well, you were the first one of us to awaken, right?
Yeah, but I don't know why or how.
Oh, well, just let it go.
Not like you'd give us a straight answer if we asked.
The one thing we do know for sure is that we're here now enjoying this awesome foot bath together.
See? Aren't you glad?
But we really do need to practice.
Yeah, I know.
So, tell me, do you think we have any chance of making it as a real idol group?
That depends. What do you think it means to be real idols?
Uh, like singing and dancing, making people feel happy, and creating lots of excitement.
If that's it, we have a lot more practicing and learning to do.
So if we work harder, do you think we'll pull it off?
Listen, I'll do all that I can.
Everything I said last time, I meant it.
I don't like to half-ass, so count me all the way in.
To the art of performing, I swore my life, and now my death.
Trust me, I know how hard showbiz can be.
As for me...
I always used to do things alone.
That's why the thought of being a team doesn't always sit well with me.
That said, if the rest of you really feel strongly about this, then maybe I'd better do my part too, right?
Thanks, Junko.
But look, the second I feel like this might not work, I'm out.
I swear you won't feel that way.
Oh yeah!
They're not gonna know what hit them when they see our concert later!
Oh, fine! How do we make that happen?
Ah, not sure.
If we do our best to service them, I'm certain the result will be pleasurable for all parties.
Wow, we need to work on your phrasing!
We should probably start by finding out everything we can about the product they're selling.
Oh yeah! We don't even know what Sagan Ship Z is supposed to do!
I say we go try it out right now!
Yeah!
So you just slap these suckers on and they make your back and shoulders feel good?
That's the general idea.
For real? That's what's up!
Says you can't put them on other people because it counts as practicing medicine.
Like I give a crap.
And besides, we're not people, we're zombies.
Uh, I don't think there's really a difference.
Hey!
Ha!
Ah!
Awesome! It's like all my muscle fatigue is melting away!
That's so cool!
Guess we absorb stuff faster!
Look at me!
I can move as much as I want and it doesn't fall off!
Ah!
You should try it, Ai!
No, I'd rather not.
I don't have any pain.
Ah!
Let's use this in the show somehow.
That way, everyone can see how well it works!
Hmm.
Ah!
Awaken now, dreamer!
Dance like no one's looking!
It's okay to go a little bit crazy!
Awaken now, dreamer!
Let your heart feel desire excitement!
Don't let the feeling ever die, die, die, die, die!
Die, die, die, die, die, die!
Hey guys!
I understand that work can be super stressful, so we hope our performance helps you unwind and recover a little bit tonight!
And there's nothing better than relaxing than Southern Chip Seed by Heatsanatha Farma Singles.
I'm number one. That's number two, three, four, five, six, and zero. Together we're Froshu Shuu. Thanks for having us.
And don't forget to keep on dreaming.
Ah, never giving up. Awaken Returner, let your heart feel courage. Let's rise up and show the world how we can go, go, go, go. High, high, high, high.
Awaken Returner, let your heart feel desire. A longing for miracles that can inspire. Awaken Returner, let your heart feel desire. Excitement, take joy wherever you can.
Give it to me.
Be for it and grab it. Don't back down. You've got it. To all the doubt you have said. Bye, bye, bye.
Our passion, devotion, our deepest emotion. Our souls will be bare when we sing. Cut in.
Songs for the soul and sorenship Z for the body. The perfect match.
The crowd really liked us. I'm so happy.
Sakura, don't take your makeup off. But it's bedtime. Not yet it isn't. Let's hit that hot spring.
What? We can't come all the way here and not get in it. But once our makeup melts off, it's all over.
Nobody's gonna be out there this late. Come on. If Kotaro finds out, we're in trouble. Here's the solution. We try not to get caught.
But what if we do? Doesn't matter, we won't. I really wish I knew where you got that unlimited confidence of yours.
Let's just say I've gotten into way more trouble than you ever have.
Is it just us? Who else did you tell us?
I think two zombies is plenty.
Less suspicious, right?
I see what your game is.
Huh?
Hey, Junko.
You're still up?
Yes, and I was planning on taking off all of my makeup after you. But then I heard...
Oh! We're not going. Too risky.
I really... wanted to go. Can we?
Heh. You hear that? Two to one.
Uh...
The water here is supposed to be really good for your skin, though! Makes it all shiny and smooth!
Maybe it'll even hard-boil that egghead of yours!
Heh!
Hmmmm...
Cowabunga!
Come on, you two! Let's get in and out while we've got time!
Huh?
Wow, I feel so alive right now!
Me too. But for the last time, we're dead.
Huh?
My skin already looks a lot smoother!
Told ya! Zombie skin absorbs stuff faster!
It's great!
Totally worth the risk! Your head's all shiny, too! Hmm.
Huh?
You know something? It looks like your egghead went rotten.
I think something just touched me!
Aw, hell no! Come out and show yourself, jackass! I got some action for you right here!
Uh...
Is that some kind of bandage?
Oh yeah, it's a Sagam Ship Z.
Damn, these things are absorbent!
Ugh, that scared me! I guess you forgot to take it off your back!
Oh my gosh, I must have! I'm sorry!
Hm, anyway...
I think today went pretty well. You?
Oh, definitely!
But, uh...
Well...
The audience did look like they were having a good time, and at the end of the day, that's most important.
Still though, our performance could use a lot of improvement.
Yeah...
I say we all keep doing our best.
So next time we can wow them with just our singing and dancing.
Okay!
Ah, sweet! It's like Maruchi just became Tamachi!
Huh?
Look, it's the lady from Hisanaka!
This is bad! She'll see us!
Go underwater!
We're zombies, so we probably don't need to breathe!
Can I hear a ghost?
Hm?
Hello?
Hm...
Hm?
Ah!
Sakura!
What?
Ah!
Ah...!
Whoa, hey, did I miss something?
I'll catch you up later.
Right now, we gotta get to the room!
Sorry, ma'am, you're passing me really quickly!
Thank you again for inviting us.
And if you decide you'd like to do business, please be in touch.
Oh, sorry about that.
Turns out she had some kind of big scare last night.
The shocks caused her to forget everything that happened yesterday.
Yikes!
You better be glad you're dead.
They say there's no bad press, but this is bad.
Who would publish that crap? Let's go kick their asses!
Sorry, it's all my fault.
Don't worry, I promise I'll be a lot more careful from now on.
There, there.
At least we got the chance to enjoy that luxurious foot bath together.
I've never had a communal experience like that.
I think it was a worthwhile journey.
We had fun!
I bet the better we all get along, the better we'll be on stage!
Ugh!
Do you think so?
Hope you're right.
And another benefit?
No more fatigue, thanks to these.
The old school chick is right.
Next time, we'll nail it.
Kay?
Yeah!
Starting now, we bust our ass and get paid!
Yay!
Yeah!
You know that's not going to solve all our problems, right?
Ugh!
Gah!
phi whaa!
Huh.
You
Yugiri speaking. The seven of us are now working toward a common goal. Isn't that a noble ideal?
Next time on Zombieland Saga Episode 5, The Nice Bird Saga in Your Heart. We hope you'll join us.